subscribenet.com 2011-06-28

# Legal and Privacy Notices - Legal - Flexera Software

Review Flexera Software’s legal and privacy notices for details on how we collect, use and protect your personal information on the website. 

Flexera Software respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us any information about yourself. On occasion, we may need your personal information to provide services that you request, or you may have the option choose to provide us with your personal information. This policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

**Information Collection  
** Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a company or home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, personal or product interests, other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

When you browse our website, you do so anonymously, unless you have previously indicated that you wish Flexera Software to remember your login and password. We don't collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our website. Like many other commercial websites, the Flexera Software website may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. Please go to "Cookies and Tracking Information" below for more information.

Flexera Software collects personal information when you register with Flexera Software for a Flexera Software account, when you use certain Flexera Software products or services, when you register to attend a seminar or participate in an online survey, when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, other product promotions, or when you submit your information to Flexera Software for any other reason. From time to time, Flexera Software receives personal information from business partners and vendors. Flexera Software only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Policy and applicable laws.

Access to certain Flexera Software web pages requires a login and a password. The use of those web pages, and the information or programs downloadable from those sites, may be governed by a written agreement between your employer and Flexera Software. Your personal information may be retained by Flexera Software to verify compliance with the agreement, log software licenses granted, to track software downloaded from those pages, or track usage of other applications available on those pages.

**Notice  
** When personal information is collected, we will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection. Flexera Software does not intend to transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the discussion entitled "Information Sharing and Disclosure" below.

If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we may transfer that information, within Flexera Software or to Flexera Software's third party service providers, including across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.

We will always give you the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving direct marketing or market research information. This means we assume you have given us your consent to collect and use your information in accordance with this Policy unless you take affirmative action to indicate that you do not consent, for instance by clicking or checking the appropriate option or box at the point of collection. In some cases, when applicable, we will provide you with the opportunity to "opt in." This means we will require your affirmative action to indicate your consent before we use your information for purposes other than the purpose for which it was submitted.

**Opting-out of Email**  
If you would like to be removed from our database, please let us know. You may opt out of receiving future mailings from our mailing lists at any time. We always include a link in the footer of our emails for this purpose.

**Cookies and Tracking Technology  
** A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of Flexera Software's website may use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of Flexera Software's website if you do so. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use/navigate through many parts of our website, except access to certain of Flexera Software's web pages require a login and password.

**How We Use Information Collected  
** Flexera Software uses information for several general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to personalize your experience on our website, to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers or other information we think you'd like to hear about either from us or from our business partners, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. We may also use your information to send you, or to have our business partners send you, direct marketing information or contact you for market research. We also use Google AdWords tracking code to track the impact of some of our marketing programs.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure  
** Because Flexera Software is a global company, your personal information may be shared with other Flexera Software offices or subsidiaries around the world. All such entities are governed by this Privacy Policy and/or are bound by the appropriate confidentiality and data transfer agreements.

Your personal information is never shared outside Flexera Software without your permission, except under conditions explained below. Inside Flexera Software, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where Flexera Software, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

Flexera Software may send your personal information to other companies or people under any of the following circumstances: when we have your consent to share the information; we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Flexera Software to provide a product or service to you (we will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose); or we want to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers or other information we think you'd like to hear about either from us or from our business partners. We will also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, to enforce our Terms of Use, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our websites.

**Data Security  
** Your Flexera Software account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. Flexera Software safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. In certain areas of our websites, Flexera Software uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

**Third Party Websites  
** Flexera Software's website contains links to other sites. Flexera Software does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy  
** Flexera Software will amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site.

**Inquiries or Suggestions  
** If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at [contracts@flexerasoftware.com](mailto:contracts@flexerasoftware.com).

This document was last updated April 1, 2008.

All contents are Copyright © 2008 Flexera Software, Inc. All rights reserved.  
Legal and Privacy Notices.
